http://www.zorb.com/privacy-policy/

Book Now!
Book Now!
Christmas & Staff Functions at ZORB
Hyper Inflation – Christmas Functions, Team Building & Corporate
News, Blogs & ZORB Stories
ZORB Myth Busters (FAQ)
Contact Us
Book Now!
Christmas & Staff Functions at ZORB
Hyper Inflation – Christmas Functions, Team Building & Corporate
News, Blogs & ZORB Stories
ZORB Myth Busters (FAQ)
Christmas & Staff Functions at ZORB
Hyper Inflation – Christmas Functions, Team Building & Corporate
News, Blogs & ZORB Stories
ZORB Myth Busters (FAQ)
Contact Us
Search
You are here:
Home / Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
PRIVACY NOTICE
We value your privacy and take every step to ensure that your information remains confidential. The statement below is a summary of the policies employed by ZORB. Please direct all enquiries to them through one of the following means.
ZORB
PO Box 12115
Rotorua 3043
Phone: +64 7 343 7676
Email: info@zorb.com
What personally identifiable information does ZORB collect from me?
We do not collect private or personal information from this web site, except where you willingly provide it.
Data is collected for the following purposes and using the following services:
Analytical user behaviour
Google Analytics
Cookies and Usage Data
As with all information, ZORB will never rent or sell your personal information.
What are cookies and how does ZORB use them?
A cookie is a small text file written to your hard drive that contains information about you. Cookies do not contain any personal information about you. We use cookies so that we can personalise your experience of the Website. If you set up your browser to reject the cookie, it may not be possible to use the Web site.
Links to Third Party Web sites
This web site may contain hyperlinks to websites operated by parties other than ZORB. Such hyperlinks are provided for your reference only. We do not control such web sites and are not responsible for their contents.
Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, unless it is processed through a Secure Credit Card System. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, ZORB cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via email. Once we receive your transmission, we make our best effort to ensure its security on our systems.
Top
Quick LinksBook NOW!
